[
    {
        "QID": "1",
        "question": "Which is considered as oldest civilization of the world ?",
        "answer-1": "Chinese",
        "answer-2": "Egyptain",
        "answer-3": "Harappan",
        "answer-4": "Mesopotamian",
        "correct": "Mesopotamian"
    },
    {
        "QID": "2",
        "question": "Who is considered as the master of Greek comedy?",
        "answer-1": "Pluto",
        "answer-2": "Aristophanes",
        "answer-3": "Aeschylus",
        "answer-4": "Sophocles",
        "correct": "Aristophanes"
    },
    {
        "QID": "3",
        "question": "Which among following is called: Gift of the Nile?",
        "answer-1": "China",
        "answer-2": "India",
        "answer-3": "Egypt",
        "answer-4": "Iraq",
        "correct": "Egypt"
    },
    {
        "QID": "4",
        "question": "In which country Aztec civilization was originated?",
        "answer-1": "Mexico",
        "answer-2": "Peru",
        "answer-3": "Panama",
        "answer-4": "Columbia",
        "correct": "Mexico"
    },
    {
        "QID": "5",
        "question": "What was the name of the atom bomb dropped by USA on Hiroshima in Japan during the second world war?",
        "answer-1": "Big Devil",
        "answer-2": "Little Boy",
        "answer-3": "Big Boy",
        "answer-4": "Little Fly",
        "correct": "Little Boy"
    },
    {
        "QID": "6",
        "question": "Who among the following empasized the 'Five Relationships'?",
        "answer-1": "Confucius",
        "answer-2": "Mahavira",
        "answer-3": "Buddha",
        "answer-4": "Lao-tse",
        "correct": "Confucius"
    },
    {
        "QID": "7",
        "question": "The historical monument Al Khazneh is located in which city?",
        "answer-1": "Tehran",
        "answer-2": "Baghdad",
        "answer-3": "Petra",
        "answer-4": "Giza",
        "correct": "Petra"
    },
    {
        "QID": "8",
        "question": "The Peloponnesian war was faught between who and who?",
        "answer-1": "Athens and Asia Minor",
        "answer-2": "Athens and Iran",
        "answer-3": "Sparta and Iran",
        "answer-4": "Sparta and Athens",
        "correct": "Sparta and Athens"
    },
    {
        "QID": "9",
        "question": "Russian revolutionary, who founded the Communist Party was?",
        "answer-1": "Karl Marx",
        "answer-2": "Lenin",
        "answer-3": "Stalin",
        "answer-4": "Trotsky",
        "correct": "Lenin"
    },
    {
        "QID": "10",
        "question": "Who said: Man is a political animal?",
        "answer-1": "Aristotle",
        "answer-2": "Karl Marx",
        "answer-3": "Lenin",
        "answer-4": "Plato",
        "correct": "Aristotle"
    }
]